翻譯: B'S Amber 阿朽
校對: apple
你知道嗎 玉米煎餅
You know what, burrito.
今天我回到辦公室才吃你
Today, I am not gonna eat you till I get to work.
這就叫有節制 抱歉了
That's discipline, my friend. Sorry about that.
后期: 大塊頭要冷靜
- 你知道嗎  - 小心
- You know what?  - Watch your back!
- 我忍不住了  - 啊
- I'm not gonna make it.  - Oh!
啊 啊
Ahh! Ahh!
壓制: BB
- 真對不起  - 我的天啊
- Oh, I am so sorry. - Oh, my God!
把錢拿走吧 就在我胸罩里
Take my money! It's in my bra!
不不不 不是這樣的
No, no, no. Nothing like that.
- 我扶你起來吧  - 真是倒霉啊
- Can I help you up?  - Oh, that was dreadful.
老天 你摔得滿臉灰
Oh, my God, you got creamed.
是呀
Yeah, I did.
不過不是很痛
But I didn't get hurt that badly,
因為幸好 我有個大屁股
because luckily, I have a big butt
在我摔倒的時候緩沖了下
and it cushioned my fall.
是啊
Yeah!
打住 我可以吐槽 你可不行
Okay, I can say that, not you.
我告訴你
You know what?
你今天應該上學的 小伙子
You should be in school, young man.
我要告訴你們訓導主任
I'm gonna call the truant officer,
他可是我一個很親密的好友
who is a close, personal friend of mine.
我都四十多了
I'm in my 40s.
你四十多
You're in your...
你怎么還穿短褲黑襪
You have shorts on and black socks.
一個穿著睡衣的女人居然這么說我
Uh, says the woman wearing pajamas.
這是醫生袍
These are scrubs.
- 噢 醫生啊  - 怎樣
- Oh! A doctor.  - Uh-huh.
- 不錯哦  - 就是
- That's pretty cool.  - It is.
那你忙不
What are you doing right now?
想來個玉米煎餅嗎
You wanna get a burrito?
我才不要玉米煎餅
No, I do not wanna get a burrito.
都九點了
It's 9:00 a.M.
好吧 如果你改變主意
Okay, well, if you change your mind...
我才不會
I will not.
我叫Graham Logan
My name is Graham Logan.
好名字 關我屁事
Cool name, doesn't matter.
很高興"碰"到你
Oh, uh, it was nice crashing into you.
好的
Okay.
看到了嗎
Did you see that?
我床上功夫也這么厲害哦
That's how good I am at sex.
明迪煩事多    第二季 第七集
電波誠譯
我愛鷹嘴豆泥
I love hummus.
不是逗你玩的
I'm not even kidding.
我可以吃這個度日
I could live on hummus.
有次我甚至還自己弄鷹嘴豆泥
I actually made hummus once.
- 是嗎  - 是的
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
很簡單的 如果你有食物加工器的話
It's very easy, if you have a food processor.
"如果"有的話
Big "If."
Mindy 你最喜歡哪種鷹嘴豆泥
Mindy, what's your favorite kind of hummus?
不 不
No, no.
嘿 各位 我想晚餐大概準備好了
Hey, everyone, I think that dinner is probably served.
對吧 Colin  Anna
Right, Colin, Anna?
要不我們進去吃飯 和其他人聊聊天吧
So why don't we go over there and talk to other people?
開什么玩笑 對號入座
Are you kidding me? Assigned seats?
你以為你奧斯卡頒獎啊
What is this, the Oscars?
沒關系 你就坐我旁邊好了
That's okay, just sit down next to me.
我想Chaz不會介意的
I'm sure Chaz will not mind.
Danny 這好像是我的位置
Hey, Danny, I think this is my seat.
呃 我們剛剛換了
Uh, we're just gonna switch it up.
走開
Get outta here.
位置安排好肯定有它的原因
There's arranged seats for a reason.
- 走走走  - 好吧
- Go, go, go, go.  - All right.
趕緊走 別壞我好事
Scram, scram. You're messing it up.
- 嘿  - 你好啊
- Hey.  - Hi.
我們肯定是做過什么壞事
We must've done something pretty bad
以至于被安排坐這么遠這么爛的座位
to get stuck all the way over here in the cheap seats.
是啊 不過也可能是他們覺得
Yeah, or maybe they think we're most likely
我們都有惹麻煩的風險
to get in some sort of trouble.
- 我是Chaz  - 你好
- Hi, I'm Chaz.  - Hi.
這是我妻子Renee
And this is my wife Renee,
這是她跟前夫生的女兒Clementine
and her daughter from her first husband, Clementine.
你怎么是一個人來
Why are you all alone?
你孩子呢
Where's your baby?
Clementine 不要那么無禮
Clementine, don't be rude to the lady.
慢著 我是在夫妻席上嗎
Wait. Am I at the couples table?
我為啥
Hey, guys, why am I
不是坐在單身席上呢
not sitting at the singles table?
每次我們想撮合你和某人
Every time we try to set you up with a guy,
你都會找出那人身上一大堆缺點 然后對我們發飆
you find something wrong with him and get mad at us.
你太挑了 所以我們不干了
You're too picky. We've given up.
你們不干了 你們不干了
You've given up? You've given up?
什么意思 不干了
What was that? You've given up?
好吧 告訴你 我剛剛給你家人下了個咒
Okay, you know what, I put a curse on your family.
Mindy 別這么說
Mindy, don't say that.
Danny 嘿 Danny Danny
Danny. Hey, Danny, Danny.
重大新聞
I have huge news.
呃 我現在正忙呢
Yeah, I'm in the middle of something right now.
Giuliani又參選市長了
Giuliani is running for mayor again.
不好意思 Mary
Excuse me, Mary.
你到底聽到了什么
What exactly did you hear?
好吧 我瞎編的
Okay, I made that up.
但是 聽著聽著
But listen, listen, listen, listen.
Colin和Anna剛剛說我太挑剔
Colin and Anna, they just told me that I'm too picky
所以他們不再幫我找對象了
and they've totally given up on setting me up.
他們說得對 你太挑了
Well, they're right. You are too picky.
去年 你不愿意和Chaz約會
Last year, you refused to go out with Chaz
就因為他名字叫Chaz
because his name was Chaz.
好吧 但是你沒告訴我他那么帥
Okay, you did not tell me that he was hot.
我對男人帥不帥沒概念 只知道有沒有男人味
Okay, I can't tell if a guy's hot, just masculine.
我繼續吃飯了 好嗎
I gotta get back to my bread, okay?
是啊 繼續跟Mary聊天吧
Yeah, you better get back to Mary.
你才不想成為這里最后一個
Don't wanna be the last person here
因為太無聊而割腕自殺的人
to slit your wrists out of boredom.
她很讓人舒緩 好嗎
Look. Look. She's calming, okay?
她對我來說就如白噪聲機一樣
She's like a white noise machine to me.
white noise machine 白噪聲機 可以用來掩蓋外界噪音從而使人平靜
好吧 那么你應該和她約會
Okay, well, then you should ask her out.
你第一次約會可以是一邊吃著餅干
And your first date could be eating crackers
一邊看天氣預報
and watching the weather channel.
起碼我不是獨自做這事情
Hey, at least I won't be doing it alone.
嗷 你竟然用叉子戳我
Ow! What... did you just stab me with a fork?
這不是大懶蟲布魯斯威利斯約翰韋恩先生嗎
Oh, look, Mr. Laid-back Bruce Willis John Wayne
Bruce Willis和John Wayne均為著名男動作影星
終于來上班啦
has finally mosied into work.
哥們 別這樣
Dude, come on.
我就不可以遲到那么個
I can't be more than, what,
五 或者十五分鐘嗎
five... teen minutes late?
大哥 一小時前你就該到這
Dude, you were meant to be here an hour ago
為明天的分娩課程做準備了
to rehearse for our birthing class tomorrow.
不 分娩課程
Oh, no. The birthing class!
- 是的  - 關于生孩子我知道些啥呢
- Yeah.  - What do I know about delivering babies?
我全知道 捏捏
Oh, right, everything. Hink.
好吧 沒必要 大家聽好了
All right, unnecessary. Everybody, listen up.
今天我有一位重要訪客
I have an important visitor coming today,
我會心懷感激
and I would appreciate it
如果你們表現得哪怕是有那么一點的有職業操守
if you could act with a little bit of dignity
而且對我略微尊重的話
and treat me like I've got some authority.
謝謝
Thank you.
好啦 你需要放松下
All right, you have gotta relax.
Morgan Morgan 你的手怎么這么濕
Oh, Morgan, Morgan! Why are your hands sopping wet?
因為我剛剛上廁所了
Because I just went to the bathroom.
你知道嗎 馬桶里的水
Do you know that the water in the toilet
比水槽里的水要干凈哦
is actually cleaner than the water in the sink?
- 我  - 是真的
- I... - It is.
不 我網上看到的
No, I read it on the Internet.
我看了一整篇關于這個的文章
I read a whole article about it.
對不起 先生 如果我不能在這抽煙
Sorry, man, if I can't smoke in here,
你也不行
neither can you.
不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no.
別鬧 Beverly 這是我爸
Nonsense, Beverly. This is my father.
他想做什么都行
He can do what he wants.
歡迎來到Shulman及其他合伙人的診所 老爸
Welcome to Shulman and associates, dad.
你兒子現在是這里的主理合伙人
The practice your son is now managing partner of.
你胖了
I see you got fat.
是啊 有點吧
Yeah, I did a bit. Yeah.
噢 看哪
Oh! What is this?
Jer小乖乖 這是你爸爸嗎
Jer-bear, is this your dad?
是的
Yes.
我要聽這家伙
You gotta tell me
小時候的童年趣事
all about this guy as a baby.
窩是這嬰兒床的管理娃啦
I'm managing baby of the crib.
要暖暖的奶瓶才能把窩喂得白白胖胖哦(英音)
Fry up my bottle so I can get fatter.
學得蠻可愛的
That's charming.
我也挺喜歡的 Jermey
I think I like this one, Jeremy.
我只在這里待一個晚上
Look, I'm only in town for the night.
今晚和我們一起吃飯吧
Why don't you join us for dinner?
好主意 我很樂意
Uh, done-zo. I'd love to.
呃我只是以為
Right, it's just I kinda thought
只是我們倆去吃飯而已
it was just gonna be the two of us.
我們倆聊啥好呢
What would we talk about?
不曉得 我們一起走過的歲月
I don't know, our shared lives?
我的兄弟 你的兒子 我的事業
My brothers, your sons, my career?
我們可以跟Peter聊這些啊
Why can't we do that with Peter there?
讓他來吧
Let him come.
你可沒幾個朋友 兒子
You haven't got that many friends, son.
好吧
Fine.
你像極了007
You look like James Bond.
人們都這么說
People often say that, yeah.
你像極了"包話事"
You look like Austin powers.
Austin Powers <王牌大賤諜>男主角
- 呃 Peter  - 超級贊啦 美女
- Oy, Peter.  - Shagadelic, baby.
Shagadelic Austin Powers的口頭禪
我不戴眼鏡 所以一點都不像
I don't have glasses, so it doesn't really work.
是的 不過你的牙齒和體重像他
Yeah, but you have the teeth and the weight.
好吧 我們晚餐見
All right, I'll see you at dinner.
各位 各位 聽我說
Everyone? Everyone! Listen up!
昨晚 Daniel Castellano侵犯了我
Last night, I was attacked by Daniel Castellano.
語言上
With words.
但依然像腦門被夾一樣讓人受傷
But still painful as though it was a blow to the head.
他說我注定孤獨一生
He told me that I was gonna die alone
因為我太挑剔了
because I'm too picky.
你是有點挑
You are a little picky.
不 我才不挑 我只是有底線
No, I am not picky. I just have standards.
你不和我兒子約會 只因為他是我兒子
You wouldn't date my son just because he's my son.
是啊 就是這個意思 謝謝你Beverly
Yes, exactly. Thank you, Beverly.
你想找個男人約會嗎 我剛好有個介紹給你
You looking for a guy? 'Cause I got one for you.
太棒了
Oh. Perfect.
我幫會兄弟 "肇事逃義"
My frat bro, "Hit n' Ron."
不行 絕對不行
Nope. No way.
你以為他因為犯事所以有這外號嗎
Oh, you think his nickname is that because he did it.
不 不 不 他是受害者
No, no, no, it happened to him.
好吧 他帥嗎
Okay. Um, is he cute?
- 不  - 性格好
- No.  - Good personality?
他是個混賬
He's kind of a dick.
- 有錢  - 沒有
- Is he rich?  - Negative.
那你為啥覺得我會喜歡這樣的人呢
Why would you think that I would like this person?
你是5分女 他是5分男
You're a five, he's a five.
啥
What?
所有人都知道我起碼是8分 8.5分
Everyone knows that I'm an 8, 8 1/2.
五分加五分就是十分好啊
Two fives make a ten.
挑剔
Picky.
蠢蛋
Stupid.
Graham 是你啊
Graham! It's you!
喲 喲
Yo, yo!
- 天啊  - 噢
- Oh, God!  - Oh!
- 對不起  - 哥們
- Sorry.  - Dude!
我沒事
I'm good.
- 噢 那個煎餅妹  - 是的
- Oh, it's bear claw!  - Yeah!
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
我找遍了所有的痞子地盤
I went to all the loser-iest places I could find...
所有的刺青店 所有的漫畫店
Every tattoo parlor, every comic book store,
所有的大麻藥店
every marijuana dispensary...
只是為了找你
All to find you.
總之 我想知道你那個跟我約會的承諾
Anyway, I wanted to know if the offer still stands
是否還能兌現
to take me out.
蘇州過后沒船坐了
That ship has sailed.
- 好吧  - 逗你呢
- Okay. - I'm just kidding.
我閑得很
I literally have nothing to do.
你想做什么呢
What are you in the mood for?
什么都行 因為我不是一個挑剔的人
Anything! Because I am not picky, my friend.
這樣啊
Ah. Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
不過我不喜歡意大利菜 中國菜和印度菜
I do not like Italian, Chinese, or Indian food,
很諷刺是嗎
ironically enough.
我的胃受不了 有結腸炎
Doesn't sit with my stomach 'cause I have colitis, so.
Danny 我要去和那個
滑板小子約會了
所以 我一點也不挑剔
你最多能撐十分鐘
LOL 我得意地笑
LOL不是這個意思
Mindy在家嗎
Is Mindy home?
殺人了 救命啊
Murderer! Ah! Hey!
是我 Graham
No! It's me. Graham.
你搞什么名堂
What the hell?
你不是說8點嗎
Well, you said 8:00.
我猜猜
Oh, let me guess.
一般那些你約會的無聊股票經紀人
The boring stockbrokers you usually date
會從大門進來
come in through the door.
是啊 他們也不會挨槍子兒
Yeah, they also don't get shot.
算你走運 我的手槍不見了
Lucky for you, I lost my handgun.
我看到消防緊急通道 就順著它爬上來了
I see a fire escape, I climb it.
如果我想要什么 就一定要得到
If I see something I want, I take it.
如果我看到一張舒服的沙發 就飛快地躺上去
And if I see a comfy sofa, oh, I like to flop on it.
啊
Ahh!
天哪
Oh, my God.
你的手肘怎么了
What happened to your elbow?
是"極限傷害"
Oh, I "Shralped" It.
什么意思
What does that mean?
這個是 1990年的時候
I got this one, uh, 1990.
我第一次國際滑板巡回表演
My first international skating tour.
喝太高 從盧浮宮摔下來
I got super loaded and fell off the Louvre.
這個呢
And this?
鎖骨受傷 在02年的極限運動會上
Broken collarbone. X-games '02.
哇 你像Kerri Strug那樣在比賽的時候受傷了嗎
Wow! You competed injured, like Kerri Strug?
Kerri Strug 美國退役體操運動員
不 我又喝高了 在頒獎的時候
No, I got super loaded and fell off the podium
從臺上摔下來了
at the medal ceremony.
早該想到
Of course.
不過那天我學到了一些東西
But I learned something that day.
醉酒阻礙了我對幸福的追求
Drinking was holding me back from following my bliss.
所以我就戒了 除了周末
So I got clean, except on weekends.
我開辦了自己的滑板公司 "懷孕的美人魚"
Started my skateboard company, pregnant mermaid.
還自己設計了標志
Designed the logo myself.
胸畫得很漂亮
Her boobs are great.
白癡都能畫好胸部 看手畫得咋樣
Any idiot can draw boobs. Check out the hand.
我最驕傲的就是手了
I'm proudest of the hand.
你身上有傷疤嗎
Mm. You have any scars?
傷全在心上
Mm, only on my heart.
不對 我真有塊疤
Oh! No, I actually have a scar.
2002年在Filene's Basement弄的
This is from Filene's Basement, 2002.
Filene's Basement全美首屈一指的名品折扣店
我當時太著急要試一件襯衫
I was rushing to try on a shirt.
別針還在里頭呢
Still had its pins in it.
差點把命丟了
I almost died that day.
哇噢
Whoa.
兩杯啤酒
Two beers.
- 謝謝  - 還有一杯雞尾酒
- Thank you. - And one Jill's naughty lemonade
果汁換成龍舌蘭
with agave instead of simple syrup
外加一點無糖可樂
and skinny bitch vodka.
謝謝 好了 謝謝
Thank you. Okay, thank you.
我的天
Good God, man!
抱歉 爸爸 不過一杯啤酒喝下去
Well, I'm sorry, dad, but a beer would cost me
我這周的減肥績點都得扣掉了
all my splurge points for the week.
如果你想減肥的話
Look, if you wanna lose some L.B.S,
和我的橄欖球隊員一起鍛煉吧
you gotta come lift with me and my rugby team.
你是你們大學橄欖球隊的
You were on your college rugby team?
這才是真漢子
There is a man.
我們更像是一支
Oh, I should say it was really more of a drinking team
愛打橄欖球的酗酒隊
with a rugby problem.
什么
What!
而且我是隊長
And I was the Captain.
再見吧 減肥績點
So long, splurge points.
我想要雞肉和豆子
Can I get chicken and frijoles?
- 這是西班牙語  - 是嗎
- That was Spanish. - Was it?
是的 我給你點了和我一樣的 垃圾玉米煎餅
Yeah, I got you what I got, which is a garbage burrito.
- 好的  - 噢
- Okay. - Oh!
等等 看這個
Hold up, check this out.
不好意思打擾了
Excuse me.
有人點了一個曲線曼妙的
Did anyone order the super hot Indian girl
性感印度女孩嗎
with the extra curves?
Graham 你會惹到麻煩的
Graham! You're gonna get in trouble.
而且 我也沒有那么性感
Besides, I'm not even that hot.
69號 你點的東西上了
And number 69, your order is up.
呃 很好的笑話 很好
No, that's... that's a good... That's a good joke.
你居然是醫生 太厲害了
I'm so impressed you're a doctor.
我只會用姜汁啤酒洗洗手肘
I probably would've just cleaned my elbow
然后用襪子包起來
with ginger ale and taped a sock on it.
窮人的健康保險啊
Poor man's health insurance, right?
你沒有健康保險
Do you not have health insurance?
如果我一直想著會受傷
I can't skate the way I need to skate
就沒法隨心所欲地滑了 你懂嗎
thinking I'm gonna get hurt, you know?
不懂 你解釋一下
I don't know. You should explain that.
你對鏡子微笑 會看見什么
If you smile into a mirror, what do you see?
我的眼角紋 一只虎牙
My crow's feet, this one fang I have
還有我得剃胡子了
that I need to get shaved down.
爛透了
It's the worst.
我相信宇宙就是一面鏡子
I believe the universe is a mirror,
它會反射你所展現的一切
and it reflects what you put out there.
我喜歡這個說法
I like that.
所以如果我買了健康保險 我就會受傷
So if I get health insurance, I'm gonna get hurt.
不 我還是不喜歡
Nope, it got dumb again.
觀念不同 各有道理
Different philosophies, both valid.
才不是呢
They're not both valid.
哎喲媽呀
Whoops-a-Daisy.
不小心用手指在奶昔上戳了個洞
I put a thumb-hole through my milkshake.
全流出來了 我可以喝你的嗎
It's all leaking out. Can I have some of yours?
剛才的想法交流真有趣
Hey, that was such an interesting exchange of ideas.
你知道我們該做什么嗎
You know what we should do?
去嗑藥 嗨起來
We should get high.
你知道嗎 Graham
You know what, Graham?
這本來會是一個很美好的夜晚
I think that's gonna have to be good night.
我完全被你的身材吸引了
My body is very attracted to your body,
但是你一說話 一切都毀了
but when you speak, my brain gets angry.
好吧 但是你還是會來的 對吧
Okay, but you're still coming over, right?
冬季性愛大賽上 我們爭取拿銅牌
Get our bronze medal at the winter sex-games.
你在說什么
What are you talking about!
今晚有哪門子事情
What about this evening would make you think
能讓你覺得我會答應你
that I would do that?
而且我為什么只能拿銅牌
And why would we only get a bronze...
我的手機
Oh. My phone!
我八年的照片都存在里面
That has, like, eight years of photos in it.
還有所有的自拍照
All my selfies!
吼 呀
Oh. Hyah!
天哪天哪
Oh, my God!
你發什么瘋
What are you doing?
我沒事
I'm okay.
Graham 快上來
Graham, get out of there!
啊
Ahh.
天哪天哪 快上來 Graham
Oh, God, get out! Get out! Graham!
這大概是你那班車了
Oh. I think this is your train.
Graham 快過來
Graham! Graham! Get out of there!
我真不敢相信你竟然冒著生命危險
Graham, I cannot believe you risked your life
去撿我的手機
just to save my cell phone.
這是我見過最勇敢的事情
That is the bravest thing that I've ever seen.
嗨 Peter
Hi, Peter.
昨晚和我爸爸過得愉快嗎
Did you have a good time with my father last night?
兄弟 你怎么了
Bro, what happened to you?
我才不會告訴你我們是奧奈達印第安月光度假區賭場的
I don't wanna say that we are the new unofficial mayors
新任非官方市長
of the Oneida Indian moon resort and casino,
因為我的襯衫上寫著呢
because then I'd be repeating what it says
就在這
on my t-shirt!
還是免費的
These things are free.
你輸了5000元 他們就送一件給你
They give them to you when you lose over $5,000.
有意思
Sounds fun.
你怎么沒去呢
How were you not there?
凌晨五點我爸爸跌跌撞撞回來的時候
Well, when my dad stumbled in at 5:00 A.M.,
他告訴我 我內褲抽屜里的邀請函不見了
he told me that my invite got lost in my panty drawer!
嗨 各位 都好嗎
Yo, everybody! How's it going?
天哪
Oh, God.
神吶
Oh, jeez!
你怎么了
What happened?
還好有護具
Luckily, I have all these pads.
頭盔是怎么回事 Brett Favre
What's up with the helmet, Brett Favre?
Brett Favre前美國橄欖球四分衛
哈 我告訴你
Uh, I'll have you know
我在和一個專業滑板運動員約會
I am dating a professional skateboarder.
所以唯一值得挑剔的就是我的疤
So the only thing picky about me are my scabs.
你和這個廢柴約會就是為了向我證明
All right, so you're dating this loser to prove a point?
也許我是真喜歡他 你也該去了解他
Or maybe I like him and you should get to know him.
事實上 我們應該一起出去吃個飯
Actually, yeah. We should all go out for dinner.
你可以叫你那個無聊的姑娘
You could invite that boring girl.
除非 你因為她很無聊 沒再聯系她了
Unless... did you not call her 'cause she's so boring
你才是那個挑剔的人
and you're the picky one?
我沒有 是行程問題
I don't... just... It's our schedules
你知道的 時間一直對不上
and, you know, phone tag.
我又不會在晚上打什么電話
I don't have the bells and whistles phone plan
做那些花里胡哨的事
with night minutes, I don't have it.
為什么在這里打給她呢
Why don't you call her from here?
- 然后我們一起出去吃晚飯  - 好極了
- We'll all go out to dinner. - Fantastic.
叫你的男人換條漂亮點的正式短褲
Tell your guy to wear his fanciest dress shorts.
好啊 叫你的Mary帶上她的個性
Okay. Tell Mary to bring her personality.
我會的 我不會
I will. I won't!
好了 我現在煩得都吃不下松餅了
Great, now you got me too worked up to eat my muffin.
你們知道嗎 Graham在25個不同的國家滑過滑板
You know, Graham skateboarded in over 25 different countries,
包括朝鮮
including north Korea,
但是好像不該說
but we're not supposed talk about it.
到處旅行確實非常有趣
Well, it's fun to be a tourist,
但Mary在日本住過
but Mary actually lived in Japan.
我兩歲的時候
When I was two.
還是三歲
Or three.
好像是兩歲 我發短信給我媽問問
Two? Let me text my mom.
沒關系 Mary 不用了
That's okay, Mary. We're good.
沒事的
Oh, no, it's okay.
反正我每隔90分鐘就會給她發短信
I text her every 90 minutes anyways.
哇 你媽媽一定很有趣吧
Wow, your mother must be really interesting.
是啊 她收集和奶牛有關的東西
Oh, boy. She collects cow stuff.
Graham "懷孕的美人魚"
Graham, so pregnant mermaid.
很古怪的名字 怎么想到的
That's a quirky name. How'd you come up with that?
我相信這一定和什么創意有關
I believe that it has to do with the fertility of new ideas.
我看到了一條
I saw one.
你看到一條美人魚
You saw a mermaid?
不 一條懷孕的美人魚
No, I saw a pregnant mermaid.
- 在夢里嗎  - 在巴厘島
- In a dream? - In Bali.
她就躺在石頭上曬太陽
She was just sunning herself on a rock.
天哪 他們為什么把醬油
God, why do they put this soy sauce
放在兩個不同的罐子里
in two different containers?
一個是低鈉的
One of 'em's low sodium.
所以Graham你是說你看見過美人魚
So Graham, you were telling us you saw a mermaid?
開始 我以為是幻覺
At first, I thought I was hallucinating,
因為我精液消耗太多有點脫水
because I was dehydrated from semen depletion.
但是她轉過身跟我說
But then she turned to me and said,
"Pergilah dalam damai"
"Pergilah dalam damai."
是巴厘語"一切和平"的意思
That means "Go in peace" In Balinese.
詭異的是
Here's the crazy part.
我不會說巴厘語
I don't speak Balinese.
確實很詭異啊
Goosebumps much?
真高興我問了
Glad I asked.
可能會有一些私人照片彈出來
There's a chance some personal photographs might pop up.
- 不要讓他們  - 我會試試
- Don't allow them to. - But... I'm gonna try.
嘿 兄弟
Hey, buddy.
只是想確定一下 我們沒事吧
Just wanna make sure we're all good.
- 你倆準備好上了嗎  - 是的
- All right, you guys ready to rock? - Yeah.
- 是的  - 行
- Um, yes. - Okay.
大家好
Hello, everybody.
我是Jeremy Reed醫生
My name is Dr. Jeremy Reed.
那看來我就是
And I guess that makes me...
Peter Prentice醫生了 如何
Dr. Peter Prentice. How about that?
講笑話 是嗎
Adding jokes, are we?
原來這是喜劇節目啊
I didn't realize it was a comedy routine.
打個趣嘛
Just bantering.
我們從臨盆的五個征兆開始吧
Let's begin with the five preliminary signs of labor.
Braxton Hicks(收縮)
Okay, Braxton Hicks.
是什么呢
Now what is that?
Toni Braxton可沒有和Taylor Hicks結婚哦
No, Toni Braxton did not marry Taylor Hicks.
Toni Braxton 美國R&B女歌手
Taylor Hicks 美國偶像第五屆冠軍
靈魂巡查隊
Soul patrol!
Soul patrol是Taylor Hicks粉絲的自稱
還記得他嗎
Remember that guy?
你們喜歡這樣 是么
You guys like that, do you?
比起我你們更喜歡這個傻帽
You prefer this lout to me?
都是跟我老爸一伙的是吧
Maybe you should get in line behind my father!
哇 哇
Whoa, whoa.
我們出了點技術問題
I think we have a technical glitch right here.
這地方出了點技術問題
I think we got a technical glitch right there.
沒錯
Yeah, yeah.
- 搞什么  - 我不知道
- What's going on?  - I don't know. I don't know.
冷靜點 行嗎
Get it together. Get it together right now.
這些人付錢是來上有趣的嬰兒課的
Because these people paid for a fun baby show.
搞定了 問題解決了
Uh, we fixed it. Fixed the glitch.
娃娃有問題
It's the doll.
收縮
Okay, Braxton Hicks.
是專指子宮收縮
Now those are specific uteri contractions.
抱歉 我有個小問題
I'm so sorry. I've got a quick question.
有準備生兒子的爸爸嗎
Any dads having sons?
嗨 爸爸們
Well, hello, dads.
準備好面對一輩子那么長的失望吧
Look forward to a lifetime of disappointment
你們的小Jeremy們不會騎自行車
because your little Jeremies can't ride a bicycle
不管你們喝得有多醉 怎么虐待他
no matter how drunk and sadistic you get.
行了
All right.
- 行了  - 因為你的兒子會說
- All right. - Because your little son is saying,
- "我不想下那個坡"  -  我們要走了
- "I don't wanna go down that hill."  - We're gonna go.
- Morgan  - "我可能爬不回來了"
- Morgan? - "Maybe I won't come back up the hill."
- 他可能就真的上不來了  - 哇
- And maybe he won't! - Whoa.
我是Morgan護士
Ah, my name is nurse Morgan.
我來給你們的寶寶取名字
I'm here to name your babies.
Grover
Grover.
John
John.
Grover
Grover.
Graham 你是賣滑板的咯
So Graham, selling skateboards.
恩
Mm.
有想過要把生意拓展到彈簧單高蹺嗎
Do you plan to branch into pogo sticks?
我不知道
I don't know.
你的專長是陰道
You specialize in vaginas.
你想拓展到乳房嗎
You hoping to branch into boobs?
我每天都檢查乳房
I check boobs every damn day,
傻了吧
so the joke's on you.
我挺喜歡你的
I like you, man.
你和我父母一樣
You're like my parents.
他們很幸福的住在安保森嚴的退休小區里
They're very happy in a gated retirement community.
我懂的
I get it.
有些獅子喜歡籠子
Some lions like a cage.
籠子
A cage?
其實是15年按揭的帥氣公寓
Uh, more like a cool condo with a 15-year fixed.
Graham可不是那種會"按揭"的人
Yeah, Graham's not really like a "Mortgage" kind of guy.
他太狂野了 不可預知
He's just too wild and unpredictable.
很性感 就像個牛仔
It's sexy, you know, like a cowboy.
你知道我們該干嘛嗎
You know what we should do?
我們該吃霸王餐
We should dine and dash.
肯定很好玩 Graham
That would be hilarious, Graham,
違反社會契約
violating a social contract.
Mindy 你喜歡這種事情 對吧
Mindy, you love that kinda stuff, right?
是的 我其實很狂野
I do, actually. I'm quite wild.
舉個例子
For instance, Mary,
我在服用一種不被FDA認可的復合維生素
I use a multivitamin that is not approved by the FDA.
FDA 食品藥品管理部門
壽司餐館在掠奪(強奸)我們的大海
You know, Sushi restaurants are raping our oceans.
你那美人魚就是這么懷上的嗎
Is that how your mermaid got pregnant?
不 是出于自愿的 和一個船長
No, it was consensual sex with a sea Captain.
我媽給我回短信了
Oh, my mom just texted me back.
我說錯了
I was wrong.
在日本的時候我四歲
I was four when I lived in Japan,
兩到三歲的時候在亞利桑那州
and from two to three, we were in Arizona,
三到四歲的時候在明尼蘇達州 然后
three to four, Minnesota, and then, I think...
Mindy 我能和你說句話嗎
Mindy, can I talk to you for a second?
很快
Just really quick.
- 工作有關的  - 當然
- It's just work related. - Sure. Love to.
拜 Graham
Bye, Graham.
馬上就好
You'll be right back.
夠了沒 跟個不懂事的小孩一樣
Would you cut it out? You're acting like a brat.
- 我  - 是的
- I am? - Yes.
青豆上了以后你就一直抓著Graham不放
You haven't let off Graham since the edamame arrived.
那是大豆
They're called soy beans.
產自愛荷華州的 好嗎
They're from Iowa, okay?
你還要忍到什么程度
How far are you gonna let this go
才愿意承認他就是個廢柴
before you admit that guy's a loser?
我喜歡的人 就是個廢柴
When I like someone, he's a loser,
我不喜歡的人 就是我太過挑剔
and if I don't like someone, I'm too picky.
你想我怎樣 Danny
What do you want me to do, Danny?
我不知道 網絡約會吧
I don't know. Web dating.
別管我怎么約會
Okay, don't give me advice on who to date.
閃開點 爺爺
Back off, grandpa.
不痛不癢 好嗎
That's not an insult, okay?
爺爺們是這個國家的脊梁
Grandfathers are the backbone of this country.
我才不要和你爭爺爺的事情
I can't get into this grandfathers thing with you.
走 伙計們
It's on, dogs.
我們吃霸王餐跑路咯
We're dining and dashing.
別別別
No, no. No.
- 天啊  - 好吧
- Oh, God. - Okay.
- 好吧  - 你想怎么辦
- Okay. What do you wanna do?
你是打算付賬呢
You gonna pay the bill,
還是和你的靈魂伴侶一起跑路
or you gonna run off with your soul mate?
我們走 我們走
Okay, we're going. We're going!
我們走 快走 快
We're going! Come on, come on, come on!
越過護欄
Oh! Over the fence!
走著
Here we go! Yeah!
來啊 翻過來
Ah. Come on! Over the fence!
這是我干過最瘋狂的事情了
This is the craziest thing I've ever done!
我要給我媽發個短信
Oh, I gotta text my mom.
上啊 Danny 上
Go, Danny! Go do it!
呀
Yah!
我能行
I got it!
- 你不行 幫下他  - 我能行
- No, you don't have it. Help him. - I got it.
像Graham那樣
Do it like Graham did it.
- 你行嗎 你能行  - 我行的
- Do you? You do. - I got it.
- 你行的  - 天啊
- Yeah, you do! - Oh, God!
好樣的
There we go.
如果Danny能行 我也能行
Okay, if Danny can do it, I can do it too.
- 嗷 嗷  - 你沒事吧
- Ow! Ow! - You okay?
- 行了 Mindy  - 我想我得破傷風了
- Come on, Mindy. - I think I have tetanus.
大屁股快點好嗎
Move your ass!
你說啥
Excuse me?
別鬧了 快點啊
No, no, no! Come on, come on, come on!
從縫里擠過來
Slide through the crack.
好主意
Okay, that's a great idea. Okay.
- 這我沒問題  - 你能行的
- I can do this. - You got it.
很好 很好
Okay, good, good, good, good, good.
你胸小是好事啊
It's a good thing your boobs are small.
大家都知道我胸大
I have huge cans. Everybody knows that.
快點
Come on, come on, come on.
好吧 好吧
All right. Okay! Okay!
你能做到的
Come on. You can do it.
就這兒
Right there.
Graham 我不行
Okay, Graham, I can't do this.
你肯定行
Sure you can!
把屁股往里縮啊
Just suck in your butt!
我辦不到
Yeah, my body can't do that.
聽我說
Come here.
你很帥 很有魅力
Look, you are beautiful and charismatic,
但我是個相信科學的女人 而你是個滿腦子不科
but I'm a woman of science and you are man of non-sci...
好吧 滿腦子荒唐玩意兒
Nonsense, actually.
我們不會有結果的
So this isn't gonna work out.
不過我很樂意跟你上床
Although, I would've loved to have had sex with you
就一次
but once.
好
Yeah.
我還以為會是4P呢
I kinda thought this was gonna end in a four-way.
唉
Ugh.
3P
Three-way?
什么
What?
2P
Two-way?
看來是1P了
One-way it is.
再見 Mindy
Good-bye, Mindy.
Pergilah dalam damai
Pergilah dalam damai.
真煩
Oh, bother.
我最喜歡的廣告
My favorite commercial right now
是一個小嬰兒
is the one where it's a baby
用男人的聲音說話
but he talks in a man's voice.
超有趣
It's really funny,
我笑翻了
and it really makes me laugh.
嗯
Mm.
你是睡著了嗎
Did you just fall asleep?
不 沒有 我醒著呢
No! I'm not sl... I'm awake.
今晚發生了很多破事兒
It's a big night, lot of sukie and...
我的毛衣有點兒 這天氣 有點厚了
My sweater's a little... It's heavy for this weather.
今晚真的很有意思
You know what? Tonight was really fun,
但是遇見Graham之后 我發現
but after meeting Graham, I just realized
我想要更有個性的對象
that I need someone with more personality.
拜
Bye.
小教堂(法) 崩潰完了嗎
Hey, Chappelle! What's with the meltdown?
我讓我爸失望了
I'm an embarrassment to my father,
讓我的家族 讓整個Reed短馬鞭帝國丟臉
to my family, to the entire Reed riding crop empire.
你 失望 不意
You? An embarrassment? I "B" To "D."
- 啥  -  我不同意
- What? - I beg to diff.
說英語 話說全
Speak in English. Speak in full words.
你來到一個新的國家
You came to a whole new country,
成為了一家超棒診所的主治醫生
became the head doctor of an awesome practice,
學會了在路的另一邊開車
you learned to drive on the opposite side of the road,
你冒險雇了一個態度糟糕的家伙
and you took a chance on a rude dude with a bad 'tude
誰也不會雇的那種
when no one would.
不是你我不會在這里
Huh? I wouldn't be here if not for you.
對我來說 你永遠是個成功的家伙
So in my book, you are always baller status.
你知道嗎
You know what?
我就是成功人士
I am baller status.
我告訴你 如果說有誰
I gotta tell you, if there's anyone
讓你的家族失望 那也是你爸爸
that's an embarrassment to your family, it's your dad.
昨晚在賭場
I mean, at the casino last night,
他找了幾個相當
he was scamming on some pretty rough
三流的妓女
Monday-night prostitutes.
老爸確實喜歡叫雞
Dad does like his prosies.
抱一個
Now bring it in!
你來干嘛
Hey! What are you doing here?
我回來付錢
I came back to pay.
真的嗎
Really?
不是因為Mary沒有更多她只記得一點點的
Mary didn't run out of Internet videos
網絡視頻可聊了嗎
to partially remember?
她正在講話的時候我睡著了
I fell asleep while she was talking.
- 天啊  - 沒錯
- Oh, my God. - Yeah.
她親我我都沒有醒過來
And I didn't even wake up when she started kissing me.
- 啥  - 聽著
- What? - Look.
這事也太常發生在你身上了吧
How often is that happening to you
- 你放棄那些  - 好吧
- that you give up those oppor...  - Okay.
就不能承認我們都很蠢嗎
Can we just admit that we were both dumb?
我們都是為了證明點什么而和別人約會
That we were both dating someone to prove a point?
一開始是我想證明給你看
Okay, it began as me trying to prove a point.
是的
Okay.
但發展到后來 我開始迫切的需要
But it evolved into a very deep need
和他上床
for me to have sex with him.
- 夠了  - 我希望這種需要能盡快消失
- Okay, that's enough. - And I hope that need goes away.
我不懂他那些紋身
I don't get the tattoo thing.
他看上去像酒吧廁所里的墻
He looked like the wall of a bar bathroom.
我覺得超性感
I thought it was super hot.
我在考慮要不要在手腕上紋一個
In fact, I was thinking of getting a tattoo on my wrist
- "呼吸"  - 呼吸
- that says "Breathe."  - Breathe?
你是怕忘了怎么呼吸嗎
Is that something you forget to do?
你怎么不在腳上紋個"走路"呢
Why don't you put "Walk" On your feet?
你該在額頭上紋個"傻瓜"
You should think about getting "Idiot" On your forehead.
好吧
Okay.
你要是要跟我吵
You know what? If you're gonna dis me,
就別吃光我的甜點
don't eat all of my dessert!
該睡咯
GO to bed!
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組